♪You are the sun in my life♪
أنتِ شمس حياتي
♪You are the light of my love♪
أنتِ نور حبي
♪When I'm lost in the dark♪
♪عندما أضيع في الظلام♪
♪Every shadow fades away♪
♪كل ظل يتلاشى♪
♪You are the sun in my life♪
أنتِ شمس حياتي
♪You are the light of my love♪
أنتِ نور حبي
♪When I'm lost in the dark♪
♪عندما أضيع في الظلام♪
♪Every shadow fades away♪
♪كل ظل يتلاشى♪
=Shine on Me= (Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
=أشرق عليّ= (ادعموا الإدارة، شاهدوا على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org)
=Episode 36=
=الحلقة 36=
Actually, there's another reason
في الواقع، هناك سبب آخر
for changing the name.
لتغيير الاسم.
You come and go all the time.
أنت تأتي وتذهب طوال الوقت.
I want to keep
أريد الاحتفاظ
a trace of you here.
أثرٌ منك هنا.
I can come over anytime.
يمكنني المجيء في أي وقت.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
But it just feels different.
لكن الأمر يبدو مختلفاً.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Why are you sorry?
لماذا أنت آسف؟
You're doing the right thing.
أنت تفعل الشيء الصحيح.
I just...
أنا فقط...
want you to know
أريدك أن تعلم
that I'll miss you.
سأفتقدك.
But I also
لكنني أيضاً
can't wait to get started.
لا أطيق الانتظار للبدء.
I think I can do a great job.
أعتقد أنني أستطيع القيام بعمل رائع.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I just wanted to apologize.
أردت فقط أن أعتذر.
Okay.
تمام.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Then
ثم
you have to swing with me 100 times.
عليك أن تتأرجح معي 100 مرة.
Come on.
تعال.
Okay.
تمام.
One.
واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
Three.
ثلاثة.
Four.
أربعة.
Five.
خمسة.
Six.
ستة.
Seven.
سبعة.
♪Two-way love, it's a fire so bright♪
♪حب متبادل، إنه نار شديدة التوهج♪
♪You are the sun in my life♪
أنتِ شمس حياتي
♪We shine together, we rise, we glow♪
♪نتألق معًا، ننهض، نشعّ ♪
♪Two hearts beating, the world will know♪
قلبان ينبضان، سيعرف العالم ذلك
♪Your laugh is music, my heart's new tune♪
ضحكتكِ موسيقى، لحن قلبي الجديد
♪Under your spell, I'm over the moon♪
♪أنا تحت سحرك، في غاية السعادة♪
♪Your touch ignites a spark so real♪
♪لمستك تشعل شرارة حقيقية♪
♪Two-way love is the magic I feel♪
♪الحب المتبادل هو السحر الذي أشعر به♪
♪Two-way love, it's a fire so bright♪
♪حب متبادل، إنه نار شديدة التوهج♪
♪You are the sun in my life♪
أنتِ شمس حياتي
♪We shine together, we rise, we glow♪
♪نتألق معًا، ننهض، نشعّ ♪
♪Two hearts beating, the world will know♪
قلبان ينبضان، سيعرف العالم ذلك
♪The world spins fast but we stay still♪
♪ العالم يدور بسرعة لكننا نبقى ثابتين ♪
♪In your arms, time dances to my will♪
♪بين ذراعيك، يرقص الزمن وفقًا لإرادتي♪
♪Your love an arrow, I see me true♪
♪حبك سهم، أرى نفسي على حقيقتي♪
♪Two-way love, I'm complete with you♪
♪حب متبادل، أنا مكتمل معك♪
♪Two hearts beating, the world will know♪
قلبان ينبضان، سيعرف العالم ذلك
Xiguang.
شيغوانغ.
Maybe I won't be able
ربما لن أكون قادراً
to work
للعمل
alongside you anymore.
لم أعد بجانبك.
But,
لكن،
if you allow it,
إذا سمحت بذلك،
I will train hard
سأتدرب بجد
and live long.
وعِش طويلاً.
I won't drift in and out
لن أتردد بين الدخول والخروج
of your world.
من عالمك.
Why...
لماذا...
Why did you suddenly
لماذا فجأة
say something so serious?
هل يمكن قول شيء بهذه الخطورة؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I didn't plan it.
لم أخطط لذلك.
So it's a bit abrupt.
لذا فالأمر مفاجئ بعض الشيء.
No.
لا.
Lin Yusen.
لين يوسن.
I...
أنا...
was a bit unprepared.
كان غير مستعد قليلاً.
I mean...
أعني...
Ask that question
اطرح هذا السؤال
again.
مرة أخرى.
Okay.
تمام.
Miss Nie,
آنسة لا،
if my heart
إذا كان قلبي
never wavers,
لا يتزعزع أبداً،
will you
سوف تفعل
allow me
اسمح لي
to be a part of your life?
أن تكون جزءًا من حياتك؟
Yes.
نعم.
I will.
أنا سوف.
♪Would we ever be close, you and me♪
هل سنكون قريبين يوماً ما، أنا وأنت؟
♪Oh, wherever you are, whatever you want♪
♪أينما كنت، ومهما أردت♪
♪Don't hesitate to call me, just let me know♪
لا تتردد في الاتصال بي، فقط أخبرني بما تريد
♪I hope you'll never forget♪
♪أتمنى ألا تنسى أبداً♪
(Two Years Later)
(بعد عامين)
♪Every moment of every day♪
♪كل لحظة من كل يوم♪
♪Our love's gonna find a way♪
حبنا سيجد طريقه
♪All this time you're in my mind♪
♪ طوال هذا الوقت أنت في بالي ♪
♪I dream of when I'll hold you every day♪
♪أحلم باليوم الذي سأحتضنك فيه كل يوم♪
♪When it won't be a scene that fades away♪
♪عندما لا يكون مشهداً يتلاشى♪
♪We'll find our way back to when♪
♪سنجد طريقنا للعودة إلى ذلك الزمن♪
♪Through all the times we were getting thru and learnt we're meant to be♪
♪خلال ​​كل الأوقات التي مررنا بها، تعلمنا أننا مقدر لنا أن نكون معًا♪
♪Would we ever be close, you and me?♪
هل سنصبح قريبين يوماً ما، أنا وأنت؟
♪Oh, wherever you are, whatever you want♪
♪أينما كنت، ومهما أردت♪
♪Don't hesitate to call me, just let me know♪
لا تتردد في الاتصال بي، فقط أخبرني بما تريد
♪I hope you'll never forget♪
♪أتمنى ألا تنسى أبداً♪
♪My heart has only you♪
قلبي لا يملك سواك
♪Every moment of every day♪
♪كل لحظة من كل يوم♪
♪Our love's gonna find a way♪
حبنا سيجد طريقه
♪Oh can you feel my heart's with you♪
♪هل تشعر بقلبي معك؟♪
♪If you ever wanna know♪
♪إذا أردت أن تعرف يوماً♪
♪I have never felt this before♪
♪لم أشعر بهذا من قبل♪
♪Would we ever be close, you and me♪
هل سنكون قريبين يوماً ما، أنا وأنت؟
♪Oh, wherever you are, whatever you want♪
♪أينما كنت، ومهما أردت♪
♪Don't hesitate to call me, just let me know♪
لا تتردد في الاتصال بي، فقط أخبرني بما تريد
♪I hope you'll never forget♪
♪أتمنى ألا تنسى أبداً♪
♪My heart has only you♪
قلبي لا يملك سواك
♪Every moment of every day♪
♪كل لحظة من كل يوم♪
♪Our love's gonna find a way♪
حبنا سيجد طريقه
(Happy Wedding)
(زفاف سعيد)
(Happiness)
(سعادة)
(Happy Wedding, Happiness)
(زفاف سعيد، سعادة)
♪A gathering storm above♪
♪عاصفة تتجمع في الأعلى♪
♪A winding path to trace♪
♪مسار متعرج يجب تتبعه♪
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Hurry.
عجل.
♪Love shouldn't rush today♪
♪لا ينبغي للحب أن يتعجل اليوم♪
♪Has yesterday's rain stopped?♪
هل توقف مطر الأمس؟
♪Today the sun shines bright♪
♪اليوم تشرق الشمس ساطعة♪
♪I who once stood in the corner's light♪
♪أنا الذي وقفتُ ذات يوم في ضوء الزاوية♪
(Shanghai Brain Science Research Center) ♪Wishing to follow you out of sight♪
(مركز شنغهاي لأبحاث علوم الدماغ) ♪أتمنى أن أتبعك حتى أغيب عن الأنظار♪
(Shuangyuan Photovoltaic Technology)
(شركة شوانغ يوان لتكنولوجيا الخلايا الكهروضوئية)
♪How long to wait if we miss once more?♪
♪كم من الوقت سننتظر إذا أخطأنا مرة أخرى؟♪
♪My heart beats only for you♪
قلبي ينبض من أجلك وحدك
♪Through rushing crowds, we made our way♪
♪ شقنا طريقنا وسط الحشود المتدفقة ♪
(Ready) Collect
(جاهز) استلم
some of their reactions
بعض ردود أفعالهم
through the eyes.
من خلال العيون.
This algorithm
هذه الخوارزمية
can be improved.
يمكن تحسينه.
After these
بعد ذلك
are all completed,
تم الانتهاء من كل شيء،
we'll see.
سنرى.
Alright?
على ما يرام؟
Okay.
تمام.
Pull it up.
ارفعه.
It's low.
إنه منخفض.
It'll get lighter and lighter.
سيصبح الأمر أخف فأخف.
(Lift left leg)
(ارفع الساق اليسرى)
Your fingers.
أصابعك.
Clench fist.
اقبض قبضتك.
(Clench left fist)
(يقبض قبضة يده اليسرى)
♪And me♪
♪وأنا♪
♪Dreams realized, dreams broken, dreams fade♪
♪أحلام تتحقق، أحلام تتحطم، أحلام تتلاشى♪
♪They're only dreams we've made♪
♪إنها مجرد أحلام صنعناها♪
♪Awake to streets aglow♪
♪استيقظ على شوارع متوهجة♪
♪With me beside you as you go♪
♪معي بجانبك وأنت تمضي♪
♪Skies darken, gloom descends, night falls♪
♪تُظلم السماء، وينزل الظلام، ويحلّ الليل♪
♪It's only rain, after all♪
♪إنها مجرد أمطار، في نهاية المطاف♪
♪We push the window wide to see skies so blue♪
نفتح النافذة على مصراعيها لنرى السماء الزرقاء الصافية
♪There'll always be me and you♪
♪سنبقى أنا وأنت دائمًا♪
(Ten Years Later, 2025)
(بعد عشر سنوات، 2025)
♪The faint morning sunlight♪
♪ضوء الشمس الخافت في الصباح♪
♪Illuminates the darkness in the eyes♪
♪يُنير الظلام في العيون♪
(State Grid, CNNC)
(شبكة الدولة، CNNC)
(PowerChina, China Huaneng)
(باور تشاينا، تشاينا هوانينغ)
♪Life is a constant rush♪
♪الحياة عبارة عن اندفاع مستمر♪
(First Step) ♪Never forget to be kind♪
(الخطوة الأولى) ♪لا تنسَ أبدًا أن تكون لطيفًا♪
♪Occasionally loneliness comes visiting♪
♪أحياناً تأتي الوحدة لزيارة المرء♪
♪Memories flash by along the way♪
♪تومض الذكريات على طول الطريق♪
(Next-Gen Battery Tech R&amp;D Progress Briefing)
( إحاطة حول التقدم المحرز في البحث والتطوير لتكنولوجيا البطاريات من الجيل التالي )
(TOPCON Battery 2025 Q2 Meeting) ♪The strength that once was broken♪
(اجتماع شركة توبكون للبطاريات، الربع الثاني من عام 2025) ♪القوة التي كانت مكسورة♪
(Guang Yu Photovoltaic)
(شركة غوانغ يو للخلايا الكهروضوئية)
♪Needs to be restored through time♪
♪يجب ترميمه عبر الزمن♪
♪Facing what comes after loss♪
مواجهة ما يأتي بعد الخسارة
♪Everything as usual♪
♪كل شيء كالمعتاد♪
♪Any hope, any despair, any confusion♪
♪أي أمل، أي يأس، أي حيرة♪
♪All continuously shaped my courage♪
♪كلها ساهمت باستمرار في تشكيل شجاعتي♪
♪How much joy and sorrow, ups and downs, warmth and coldness♪
♪كم من الفرح والحزن، والتقلبات، والدفء والبرودة♪
As planned,
كما هو مخطط له،
the new photovoltaic power station is completed.
تم الانتهاء من محطة الطاقة الكهروضوئية الجديدة .
It utilizes TOPCON battery technology.
تستخدم تقنية بطاريات توبكون.
Total power generation capacity
إجمالي قدرة توليد الطاقة
has exceeded 6.6 million kilowatts.
تجاوزت قدرتها 6.6 مليون كيلوواط.
That's fantastic.
هذا رائع.
♪I still choose me, smiling as always♪
♪ما زلت أختار نفسي، مبتسمة كالعادة♪
♪Even after loss, I can still appear♪
♪حتى بعد الخسارة، ما زلت أستطيع الظهور♪
♪Everything as usual♪
♪كل شيء كالمعتاد♪
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Did the clinical trial succeed?
هل نجحت التجربة السريرية؟
Yeah.
نعم.
So I wanted to see you
لذلك أردت رؤيتك
and
و
the PV station.
محطة الطاقة الشمسية الكهروضوئية.
Come on.
تعال.
Look.
ينظر.
These
هؤلاء
are all our achievements.
كل هذه إنجازاتنا.
♪With regrets, choices, and beliefs♪
♪مع الندم والاختيارات والمعتقدات♪
♪Life turns out to be just like this♪
♪تبدو الحياة هكذا تماماً♪
♪I still choose me, smiling as always♪
♪ما زلت أختار نفسي، مبتسمة كالعادة♪
♪Even after loss, I can still appear♪
♪حتى بعد الخسارة، ما زلت أستطيع الظهور♪
♪Everything as usual♪
♪كل شيء كالمعتاد♪
♪After the loss, the world remains the same♪
♪بعد الخسارة، يبقى العالم كما هو♪
(2028)
(2028)
Dr. Lin.
د. لين.
Getting off work?
هل ستنتهي من العمل؟
Yeah, Taiji.
نعم، تاي تشي.
I'm off to the kindergarten.
أنا ذاهب إلى روضة الأطفال.
So your daughter
إذن ابنتك
is still in kindergarten.
لا يزال في الروضة.
So you had a daughter later in life.
إذن أنجبت ابنة في وقت متأخر من حياتك.
Thanks for the comment.
شكراً على التعليق.
Taiji.
تاي تشي.
Get off work early.
انصرف من العمل مبكراً.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I will get off work on time.
سأغادر العمل في الوقت المحدد.
Robots never work overtime.
لا تعمل الروبوتات أبداً ساعات إضافية.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Dr. Lin.
د. لين.
Hello, Doctor.
مرحباً يا دكتور.
I'm happy to see you on time.
يسعدني رؤيتك في الموعد المحدد.
According to the itinerary,
بحسب خط سير الرحلة،
(Signing Ceremony) you're heading to
(حفل التوقيع) أنت متجه إلى
Sunshine Kindergarten
روضة صن شاين
to pick up your daughter.
لاصطحاب ابنتك.
After dinner with her,
بعد تناول العشاء معها،
you'll head to the airport
ستتوجه إلى المطار
for your wife.
لزوجتك.
Her flight
رحلتها
will arrive at 7:30 PM,
سيصل في الساعة 7:30 مساءً،
landing on time
الهبوط في الموعد المحدد
at Shanghai Pudong International Airport.
في مطار شنغهاي بودونغ الدولي.
Are there any changes
هل هناك أي تغييرات؟
to the above itinerary?
هل ينطبق ذلك على خط سير الرحلة المذكور أعلاه؟
No.
لا.
(Signing Ceremony) Do you wish to replay
(حفل التوقيع) هل ترغب في إعادة التشغيل؟
the news you've played
الأخبار التي قمت بتشغيلها
ten times this morning?
عشر مرات هذا الصباح؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
(Signing Ceremony) (Leading Chinese BIPV company)
(حفل التوقيع) (شركة صينية رائدة في مجال أنظمة الطاقة الشمسية الكهروضوئية المدمجة في المباني)
(Guang Yu Photovoltaic,)
(غوانغ يو للخلايا الكهروضوئية)
(partnered with Sheng Yuan,)
(بالشراكة مع شينغ يوان،)
(has secured a major BIPV project)
(حصل على مشروع كبير للخلايا الكهروضوئية المدمجة في المباني)
("Oasis City")
(مدينة الواحة)
(in the Middle East.)
(في الشرق الأوسط.)
(Signing Ceremony 2028) (It further solidifies)
(حفل التوقيع 2028) (يعزز ذلك أكثر)
(its leading position)
(موقعها الرائد)
(in the BIPV sector)
(في قطاع الخلايا الكهروضوئية المدمجة في المباني)
(home and abroad.)
(في الداخل والخارج).
(Over the past decade, Guang Yu Photovoltaic has)
(على مدى العقد الماضي، قامت شركة غوانغ يو للطاقة الشمسية)
(not only advanced)
(ليس فقط متقدمًا)
(in traditional PV modules,)
(في وحدات الخلايا الكهروضوئية التقليدية،)
(but also expanded)
(ولكن تم توسيعه أيضًا)
(into BIPV)
(في الخلايا الكهروضوئية المدمجة في المباني)
(and energy storage.)
(وتخزين الطاقة).
(Its PV tiles,)
(بلاطاتها الكهروضوئية،)
(PV curtain walls,)
(جدران ستائرية كهروضوئية)
(and other BIPV materials)
(وغيرها من مواد الخلايا الكهروضوئية المدمجة في المباني)
(are sold worldwide,)
(تباع في جميع أنحاء العالم)
(generating annual profits)
(تحقيق أرباح سنوية)
(of billions of RMB.)
(بمليارات اليوانات الصينية).
(Sunshine Kindergarten)
(روضة صن شاين)
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Zip up your backpack.
أغلق حقيبة ظهرك.
- Bye.
- وداعا وداعا.
Bye.
الوداع.
Dad.
أب.
(Xingheng) Are we going to
(شينغهينغ) هل سنذهب إلى
pick up Mommy?
هل ستأخذ أمي؟
Yes, Xingheng.
نعم، شينغهنغ.
After dinner,
بعد العشاء،
we'll pick up Mommy.
سنذهب لأخذ أمي.
Say goodbye to your friends.
ودّع أصدقاءك.
Bye, Lin.
مع السلامة يا لين.
Say goodbye.
قل وداعاً.
Bye, Xingheng.
وداعا، شينغهنغ.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Dad, I won't eat.
أبي، لن آكل.
I want to see Mom sooner.
أريد أن أرى أمي عاجلاً.
She is still on the plane.
لا تزال على متن الطائرة.
I can't really make
لا أستطيع حقاً أن أفعل
the plane fly faster.
الطائرة تطير بشكل أسرع.
Plus, if she
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، إذا كانت
finds out that
يكتشف أن
we don't eat,
نحن لا نأكل،
I'll lose points.
سأخسر نقاطاً.
Thanks to you,
شكراً لك،
I have very few
لدي القليل جداً
points left.
النقاط المتبقية.
I never told on you.
لم أوشي بك أبداً.
(Sunshine Kindergarten) Two days ago, you told Mommy
(روضة صن شاين) قبل يومين، أخبرتِ ماما
that I didn't
أنني لم أفعل
braid your hair.
قومي بتضفير شعرك.
I lost five points.
خسرت خمس نقاط.
This morning, you told Mommy
أخبرتِ أمي هذا الصباح
I watched the rocket launch instead of watching cartoons with you.
شاهدت إطلاق الصاروخ بدلاً من مشاهدة الرسوم المتحركة معك.
I lost another five points.
خسرت خمس نقاط أخرى.
Daddy's points are all gone.
لقد نفدت جميع نقاط أبي.
Xingheng.
شينغهنغ.
Mom is strict.
أمي صارمة.
My teacher only deducts one point each time.
لا يخصم أستاذي سوى نقطة واحدة في كل مرة.
So we need to behave
لذا علينا أن نتصرف بشكل لائق
and eat, okay?
وتناول الطعام، حسناً؟
Okay.
تمام.
I will tell Mommy
سأخبر أمي
that you're the best
أنك الأفضل
and ask for your points back.
واطلب استعادة نقاطك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Let me check again.
دعني أتحقق مرة أخرى.
Now Mommy won't
الآن لن تفعل أمي
find anything to criticize.
ابحث عن أي شيء تنتقده.
Mommy's here.
أمي هنا.
Yusen.
يوسن.
- Xingheng. - Mommy.
- شينغ هينغ. - أمي.
Sweetie.
حبيبي.
♪You said you like summer♪
♪قلتَ إنك تحب الصيف♪
♪I only remember the curve of your smile♪
لا أتذكر سوى انحناءة ابتسامتك
You're finally back.
لقد عدت أخيرًا.
Great job.
عمل رائع.
It's been a long time.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
♪Like the dialogue of an old movie♪
♪مثل حوار فيلم قديم♪
Come down.
إهدأ.
- What's wrong? - Be good.
- ما الخطب؟ - كن مطيعاً.
Mommy.
أمي.
Flowers.
الزهور.
There are flowers!
هناك أزهار!
Welcome home, Mommy.
أهلاً بعودتك إلى المنزل يا أمي.
Thank you, Xingheng.
شكرا لك، شينغهنغ.
Daddy took me to buy them,
أخذني أبي لشرائها،
but I used my pocket money.
لكنني استخدمت مصروف جيبي.
Daddy's so stingy.
أبي بخيل جداً.
Good thing Mommy only brought
لحسن الحظ أن أمي أحضرت فقط
chocolate for you.
شوكولاتة لك.
No chocolate for Daddy.
لا شوكولاتة لأبي.
Mommy's the best.
أمي هي الأفضل.
Did you miss Mommy?
هل اشتقتِ لأمكِ؟
Xingheng.
شينغهنغ.
Auntie wants a hug. Come on.
تريد عمتي عناقاً. هيا.
Auntie, flowers.
يا خالتي، زهور.
Wishing you success from the start,
أتمنى لك التوفيق منذ البداية،
and victory wherever you go.
والنصر أينما ذهبت.
Sweetie.
حبيبي.
Auntie loves you so much.
عمتي تحبك كثيراً.
You even know such difficult idioms.
بل إنك تعرف مثل هذه التعابير الاصطلاحية الصعبة.
You're amazing.
أنت رائع.
Xingheng,
شينغهنغ،
don't go back with Mommy and Daddy.
لا تعودي مع أمي وأبي.
Stay with Auntie in Shanghai for a few days.
أقم مع عمتي في شنغهاي لبضعة أيام.
Did you bring chocolate?
هل أحضرت معك شوكولاتة؟
Of course, I did.
بالطبع فعلت.
I also bought
اشتريت أيضًا
other yummy things.
أشياء لذيذة أخرى.
I'll finish what Mommy brought first,
سأنهي ما أحضرته أمي أولاً،
and then go to your house.
ثم اذهب إلى منزلك.
Little smarty-pants.
يا له من ذكي صغير.
Yusen.
يوسن.
I'm so happy
انا سعيد للغاية
your clinical applications of the brain-computer interface
تطبيقاتك السريرية لواجهة الدماغ والحاسوب
are a huge success.
لقد حققوا نجاحاً باهراً.
It will help
سيساعد ذلك
paralyzed patients
المرضى المصابون بالشلل
regain independence.
استعادة الاستقلال.
I saw the news before I left.
لقد شاهدت الأخبار قبل أن أغادر.
I just got too busy
لقد انشغلت كثيراً
to congratulate you in time.
لأهنئك في الوقت المناسب.
You're amazing.
أنت رائع.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
It's the achievements of our colleagues
إنها إنجازات زملائنا
from various specialties.
من تخصصات مختلفة.
Will it soon be possible
هل سيكون ذلك ممكناً قريباً؟
to restore sight to the blind?
لإعادة البصر إلى المكفوفين؟
In current clinical trials,
في التجارب السريرية الحالية،
higher-density electrodes
أقطاب كهربائية ذات كثافة أعلى
already help the blind
يساعد المكفوفين بالفعل
perceive the three primary colors.
إدراك الألوان الأساسية الثلاثة.
Not only us,
ليس نحن فقط،
but many other research teams
لكن العديد من فرق البحث الأخرى
are working on it.
يعملون على ذلك.
That's great.
هذا رائع.
I'm grateful to be born in this era.
أنا ممتن لأنني ولدت في هذا العصر.
And I need to
وأنا بحاجة إلى
report something.
أبلغ عن شيء ما.
While in Saudi Arabia,
أثناء وجودي في المملكة العربية السعودية،
your wife kept searching
استمرت زوجتك في البحث
for your news,
لأخباركم،
replaying each piece
إعادة تشغيل كل مقطوعة
on loop.
بشكل متكرر.
Got a problem?
هل لديك مشكلة؟
I was keeping up with cutting-edge tech.
كنت أواكب أحدث التقنيات.
What a coincidence.
يا لها من مصادفة!
I also played the news about
قمت أيضاً بتشغيل الأخبار حول
you guys'
يا رفاق'
BIPV project
مشروع الخلايا الكهروضوئية المدمجة في المباني
in the Middle East on loop.
في الشرق الأوسط بشكل متكرر.
You can drop the "you guys" part.
يمكنك حذف عبارة "أنتم يا رفاق".
I know it wasn't about me.
أعلم أن الأمر لم يكن يتعلق بي.
I knew you'd
كنت أعرف أنك ستفعل
come to pick up Xiguang.
تعال لأخذ شيغوانغ.
I also called someone
اتصلت بشخص ما أيضاً
to pick me up.
ليقلني.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Sheng Xingle.
شنغ شينغل.
I am back.
أنا عدت مرة أخرى.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Mommy will cook for you.
ستطبخ لكِ ماما.
- What? - You can't find fault, huh?
- ماذا؟ - ألا تستطيع أن تجد خطأً، أليس كذلك؟
Ten more minutes?
عشر دقائق أخرى؟
You're done for, Sheng Xingle.
لقد انتهى أمرك يا شينغ شينغلي.
Your esports team
فريقك في الرياضات الإلكترونية
won't get another penny
لن أحصل على فلس آخر
from me this year.
مني هذا العام.
Once Xingle is here,
بمجرد وصول زينجل،
let's have dinner.
لنتناول العشاء.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
You're going back to Suzhou.
ستعود إلى سوتشو.
Besides, absence makes the heart grow fonder.
فضلاً عن ذلك، فإن البعد يزيد الشوق.
I don't want to be a third wheel.
لا أريد أن أكون دخيلاً.
Where is your car?
أين سيارتك؟
At P2.
في P2.
Different floor.
طابق مختلف.
Here's your baby.
هذا طفلك.
Daddy braided your hair?
هل قام أبي بتضفير شعرك؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Xingheng.
شينغهنغ.
Take one for now.
خذ واحدة الآن.
I'll give you the other one
سأعطيك الآخر
when you come to my house.
عندما تأتي إلى منزلي.
Say thank you.
قل شكراً.
Thank you, Auntie.
شكراً لكِ يا خالتي.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Take care.
يعتني.
The company car is here.
سيارة الشركة هنا.
Take the company car back.
أعد سيارة الشركة.
Got it, Boss. Don't worry.
فهمت يا رئيس. لا تقلق.
We know the way.
نحن نعرف الطريق.
It's been a long trip.
لقد كانت رحلة طويلة.
Stay home
ابقَ في المنزل
for the next few days.
خلال الأيام القليلة القادمة.
Come back on Monday.
عد إلينا يوم الاثنين.
Paid holiday.
إجازة مدفوعة الأجر.
You're the best.
أنت الأفضل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Stop being a third wheel.
توقف عن كونك دخيلاً.
- Here. - Thanks.
- تفضل. - شكراً.
We're off now.
لقد انطلقنا الآن.
Take care.
يعتني.
Okay, let's go.
حسناً، لنذهب.
Let's go home.
هيا بنا إلى المنزل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Off we go.
هيا بنا.
You used
لقد استخدمت
four hair clips?
أربعة مشابك شعر؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You should use six.
يجب عليك استخدام ستة.
The more, the better?
كلما زاد العدد كان ذلك أفضل؟
Points for you.
نقاط لك.
Okay.
تمام.
Off we go.
هيا بنا.
I saw her before boarding.
رأيتها قبل الصعود إلى الطائرة.
Right in front of us.
أمامنا مباشرة.
I thought you'd
ظننت أنك ستفعل
say hello.
قل مرحباً.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I remember years ago,
أتذكر قبل سنوات،
when you, Kevin, and I
عندما كنت أنت وكيفن وأنا
left Hua Ya to start our own venture.
غادرنا هوا يا لنبدأ مشروعنا الخاص.
After securing
بعد التأمين
our first FOF,
أول فعالية لنا على منصة FOF،
we celebrated.
احتفلنا.
And you got drunk
وسكرت
and told me your story with her.
وأخبرتني قصتك معها.
Just that once.
لمرة واحدة فقط.
But I remember it clearly.
لكنني أتذكر ذلك بوضوح.
You said you wanted
قلت إنك تريد
to tell her you were sorry.
أن تخبرها أنك آسف.
Not disturbing her
عدم إزعاجها
is the best apology now.
هذا أفضل اعتذار في الوقت الحالي.
Success forgives the intrusion.
النجاح يغفر التدخل.
Chris,
كريس،
she's not like that.
هي ليست كذلك.
This is human nature.
هذه هي الطبيعة البشرية.
She can be an exception.
قد تكون استثناءً.
You struggled
لقد عانيت
the whole trip?
الرحلة بأكملها؟
No.
لا.
I actually slept
لقد نمت بالفعل
on the plane.
على متن الطائرة.
Soundly.
بشكل سليم.
I dreamed about the past.
حلمت بالماضي.
But seriously,
لكن بجدية،
you haven't seen her
لم ترها
all these years?
كل هذه السنوات؟
That's weird.
هذا غريب.
Didn't you alumni get married?
ألم تتزوجوا أنتم الخريجون؟
You didn't run into her?
ألم تصادفها؟
Maybe
ربما
it's taken back.
تم التراجع عنه.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Why didn't you wait for me?
لماذا لم تنتظرني؟
My suitcase
حقيبتي
came out just now.
صدر للتو.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Oh.
أوه.
Isn't he
أليس كذلك؟
my never-met
لم أقابل قط
life-saver?
منقذ للحياة؟
You still remember him after a decade.
ما زلت تتذكره بعد مرور عقد من الزمان.
Come on.
تعال.
He didn't
لم يفعل
let me thank him in person,
دعني أشكره شخصياً،
but at least
لكن على الأقل
I remember his name.
أتذكر اسمه.
Besides,
بجانب،
he's now China's
هو الآن رئيس الصين
preeminent figure
شخصية بارزة
in brain-computer interface
في واجهة الدماغ والحاسوب
and brain science research.
وأبحاث علم الدماغ.
I work in investment.
أعمل في مجال الاستثمار.
Of course,
بالطبع،
I would know him.
كنت سأعرفه.
My life-saver
منقذي
truly stands tall.
شامخ حقاً.
Impressive.
بديع.
Is that his wife?
هل هذه زوجته؟
Why does it look
لماذا يبدو الأمر كذلك؟
a bit familiar?
مألوف بعض الشيء؟
But I can't recall.
لكنني لا أستطيع التذكر.
Because you had amnesia.
لأنك كنت تعاني من فقدان الذاكرة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I lost my memory at Changbai Mountains.
فقدت ذاكرتي في جبال تشانغباي.
That was a decade ago.
كان ذلك قبل عقد من الزمان.
How did I know her?
كيف عرفتها؟
You did see her there.
لقد رأيتها هناك.
Seriously?
بجد؟
I remember now.
أتذكر الآن.
She's the head of Guang Yu.
هي رئيسة شركة غوانغ يو.
That explains it.
هذا يفسر الأمر.
She's married to Dr. Lin?
هل هي متزوجة من الدكتور لين؟
How did that happen?
كيف حدث ذلك؟
They kept it a secret.
لقد أبقوا الأمر سراً.
No one knows
لا أحد يعلم
they're married.
هما متزوجان.
They're impressive.
إنها مثيرة للإعجاب.
When I first met her
عندما التقيت بها لأول مرة
at Changbai Mountains,
في جبال تشانغباي،
I only
أنا فقط
found her pretty.
وجدتها جميلة.
But now,
لكن الآن،
she's become
لقد أصبحت
a big name in new energy.
اسم كبير في مجال الطاقة الجديدة.
Chris,
كريس،
you're amazing too.
أنت رائع أيضاً.
Of course.
بالطبع.
I'm a partner at Sequence Quant,
أنا شريك في شركة سيكوينس كوانت،
after all.
على كل حال.
Alright,
على ما يرام،
excellent Ms. Chris,
ممتاز يا آنسة كريس،
what's for dinner?
ماذا سنتناول على العشاء؟
I'm dying for Chinese food.
أنا أتوق بشدة لتناول الطعام الصيني.
You guys go ahead.
انطلقوا يا رفاق.
I need to comfort
أحتاج إلى أن أُريح نفسي.
my poor boyfriend
حبيبي المسكين
who got stood up
الشخص الذي تم تجاهله
twice.
مرتين.
Traitor.
خائن.
♪I can only call out loud♪
♪لا أستطيع إلا أن أنادي بصوت عالٍ♪
♪To mask my awkward sorrow♪
♪لإخفاء حزني المحرج♪
♪Clutching regret tightly in both hands♪
♪أمسك بالندم بقوة بكلتا يدي♪
♪Tossing it towards the dazzling fireworks♪
♪رميها باتجاه الألعاب النارية المبهرة♪
♪Even if love was so brief♪
♪حتى لو كان الحب قصيرًا جدًا♪
♪Wishing you well is the kindness I choose♪
♪أتمنى لك الخير، هذا هو اللطف الذي أختاره♪
♪You're not coming back♪
♪لن تعود♪
Three pieces a day.
ثلاث قطع يومياً.
You can only have one a day if you eat it daily.
لا يمكنك تناول أكثر من واحدة في اليوم إذا كنت تأكلها يومياً.
And brush your teeth.
ونظف أسنانك بالفرشاة.
But Mom bought so much.
لكن أمي اشترت الكثير.
It'll go bad if I eat too slowly.
سيفسد الطعام إذا أكلت ببطء شديد.
I promise it won't go bad.
أعدك أن الأمور لن تسوء.
Or I'll pay for it.
أو سأدفع ثمنها.
Mommy.
أمي.
Even though I bought it,
على الرغم من أنني اشتريته،
I'm only responsible for buying it.
أنا مسؤول فقط عن شرائه.
Daddy distributes it.
أبي يوزعها.
And you eat it.
وتأكله.
Our roles are clear, right?
أدوارنا واضحة، أليس كذلك؟
One piece a day is too little.
قطعة واحدة في اليوم قليلة جداً.
I can't even taste the flavor.
لا أستطيع حتى تذوق النكهة.
Sweetie.
حبيبي.
Well...
حسنًا...
Mommy needs to brush her teeth
ماما بحاجة إلى تنظيف أسنانها
and put on a face mask.
وضع قناع الوجه.
So, discuss it with Dad.
لذا، ناقش الأمر مع والدك.
Dad,
أب،
I want three pieces.
أريد ثلاث قطع.
That is too much.
هذا كثير جداً.
Your teeth will go bad.
ستتدهور أسنانك.
I won't be friends with you.
لن أكون صديقاً لك.
Then,
ثم،
how about two pieces per day?
ماذا عن قطعتين في اليوم؟
- Okay. - We...
- حسناً. - نحن...
Okay.
تمام.
Pinky promise then.
إذن، أعدك وعداً.
Okay, sealed.
حسناً، تم الإغلاق.
Okay, it's settled then.
حسناً، تم الاتفاق إذن.
Sleep.
ينام.
Come on.
تعال.
She's asleep?
هل هي نائمة؟
Yeah.
نعم.
We bargained for ages
لقد تفاوضنا لفترة طويلة
and agreed on two pieces a day.
واتفقوا على إنتاج قطعتين موسيقيتين يومياً.
She agreed to sleep.
وافقت على النوم.
You sure ran off quickly,
لقد هربت بسرعة كبيرة،
leaving me to deal with her.
تركتني أتعامل معها.
I'm too soft-hearted.
أنا رقيق القلب للغاية.
An important task like
مهمة مهمة مثل
distributing snacks
توزيع الوجبات الخفيفة
shall be entrusted
يُعهد به
to the nutrition expert,
إلى خبير التغذية،
Dr. Lin.
د. لين.
A kiss as a reward.
قبلة كمكافأة.
Is the reward
هل المكافأة
just symbolic?
مجرد رمزية؟
I'll take her to her room.
سآخذها إلى غرفتها.
♪Raindrops♪
♪قطرات المطر♪
♪Falling out of time, when you are near♪
♪الخروج عن الزمن، عندما تكون قريبًا♪
♪Singing, in silence♪
♪غناء، في صمت♪
♪And the world stops♪
♪ ويتوقف العالم ♪
♪Spinning out of line, so uncontrollably♪
♪يخرج عن السيطرة، بشكل لا يمكن السيطرة عليه♪
♪When you are near me♪
♪عندما تكون بالقرب مني♪
♪Am I dreaming♪
♪هل أنا أحلم؟♪
♪I'll be there♪
سأكون هناك
I miss you so much.
أفتقدك كثيرًا.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
Tired?
مرهق؟
Just a little.
قليلاً فقط.
But I slept a bit
لكنني نمت قليلاً
on the plane.
على متن الطائرة.
And now,
والآن،
I'm a bit too awake.
أنا مستيقظ أكثر من اللازم.
So...
لذا...
I think I can
أعتقد أنني أستطيع
play on my phone.
ألعب على هاتفي.
♪The rain stopped♪
♪توقف المطر♪
♪The clouds are parting skies are clear♪
♪تتبدد الغيوم، والسماء صافية♪
♪We're dancing in the moonlight♪
♪نرقص تحت ضوء القمر♪
♪In my mind♪
♪في ذهني♪
♪I'll be dreaming♪
♪سأكون أحلم♪
♪I'll be there♪
سأكون هناك
♪For the day when you would come to me♪
♪في اليوم الذي ستأتي فيه إليّ♪
Congrats.
تهاني.
You've realized that vision.
لقد حققت تلك الرؤية.
What vision?
أي رؤية؟
♪Until that day, I'll play the game♪
♪حتى ذلك اليوم، سأستمر في لعب اللعبة♪
♪I'll dream away, it'll be the same, 'till♪
سأحلم، وسيبقى الأمر على حاله، إلى أن
Go to sleep.
اذهب إلى النوم.
♪Until you came to me♪
♪حتى أتيت إليّ♪
What's for breakfast?
ماذا سنتناول على الفطور؟
Swordfish wontons.
ونتون سمك أبو سيف.
Your mom had someone
كان لدى والدتك شخص ما
deliver
يسلم
some wontons yesterday.
بعض الفطائر الصينية أمس.
Mom is busier
الأم أكثر انشغالاً
than any of us now.
أكثر مما هو عليه الحال بالنسبة لأي منا الآن.
She's always traveling all over,
إنها تسافر باستمرار إلى أماكن كثيرة،
never around.
لا يوجد أبداً.
I remember that
أتذكر ذلك
you encouraged her
لقد شجعتها
to go around in her sixties.
أن تتجول في الستينيات من عمرها.
Because she's much happier
لأنها أكثر سعادة بكثير
when she's busy.
عندما تكون مشغولة.
She does look
إنها تبدو كذلك
more energetic.
أكثر نشاطاً.
I'll cook them.
سأقوم بطهيها.
Okay.
تمام.
In a few minutes,
في غضون دقائق قليلة،
Xingheng will wake up too.
سيستيقظ شينغهنغ أيضاً.
Did you say something
هل قلت شيئاً؟
before bed last night?
قبل النوم الليلة الماضية؟
Something about realizing a vision?
شيء ما يتعلق بتحقيق رؤية؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Congratulations
تهانينا
on selling your products
بيع منتجاتك
to the Middle East
إلى الشرق الأوسط
and building BIPV power systems
وبناء أنظمة الطاقة الكهروضوئية المدمجة في المباني
in the deserts of the Oil Kingdom.
في صحاري مملكة النفط.
(What else did I say?)
(ماذا قلت أيضاً؟)
You also said
قلت أيضاً
that you'd sell the products
أنك ستبيع المنتجات
to the Middle East
إلى الشرق الأوسط
and build massive BIPV power systems
وبناء أنظمة طاقة كهروضوئية ضخمة مدمجة في المباني
in the deserts of the Oil Kingdom.
في صحاري مملكة النفط.
All "Made in China".
جميعها "صنع في الصين".
When did I
متى فعلت ذلك؟
say those things?
هل تقول هذه الأشياء؟
You said in a previous meeting
قلت في اجتماع سابق
not to limit our focus to the markets of Europe and America,
عدم حصر تركيزنا على أسواق أوروبا وأمريكا،
but also pay attention
لكن انتبه أيضاً
to Asian,
إلى الآسيويين،
Latin American, and African countries.
دول أمريكا اللاتينية والدول الأفريقية.
So I thought about it.
لذا فكرت في الأمر.
As you always talk about the Northwest strategy,
كما تتحدث دائمًا عن استراتيجية الشمال الغربي،
the Middle East is also full of deserts
الشرق الأوسط مليء أيضاً بالصحاري
with intense sunlight, perfect for such projects.
مع ضوء الشمس الشديد، فهو مثالي لمثل هذه المشاريع.
I found a pattern
لقد وجدت نمطًا
and generalized.
وتعميمياً.
I attributed
عزوت ذلك إلى
such wise words
كلمات حكيمة
to you.
لك.
Aren't you pleased?
ألا يسرك ذلك؟
You still remember that nonsense
ما زلت تتذكر ذلك الهراء
so long ago?
منذ زمن بعيد؟
Of course, I remember what my wife says.
بالطبع، أتذكر ما تقوله زوجتي.
What if you quiz me?
ماذا لو سألتني سؤالاً؟
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتفوه بالهراء.
Have I ever quizzed you?
هل سبق لي أن سألتك سؤالاً؟
You made it.
لقد نجحت.
So it wasn't nonsense.
إذن لم يكن الأمر هراءً.
Young Miss Nie
الآنسة ني الصغيرة
was ambitious
كان طموحاً
and insightful.
وبصيرة.
And you too.
وأنت أيضاً.
You made it, Dr. Lin.
لقد نجحت يا دكتور لين.
(Medical education)
(التعليم الطبي)
reaches far beyond the clinic
يتجاوز نطاقه حدود العيادة بكثير
and the operating room.
وغرفة العمليات.
I can do many things.
أستطيع فعل أشياء كثيرة.
There is always
هناك دائماً
a different path.
مسار مختلف.
There are things to do.
هناك أشياء يجب القيام بها.
My hand is ruined.
يدي تالفة.
Without it,
بدونه،
I am useless?
أنا عديم الفائدة؟
My knowledge
معرفتي
is the most valuable.
هو الأكثر قيمة.
Mom, Dad, good morning.
أمي، أبي، صباح الخير.
Is there anything to eat? I'm hungry.
هل يوجد شيء للأكل؟ أنا جائع.
You got up by yourself.
لقد نهضت بمفردك.
You're amazing.
أنت رائع.
Look.
ينظر.
Daddy is making wontons.
أبي يصنع الوانتون.
The ones that Grandma sent.
تلك التي أرسلتها جدتي.
Almost ready.
جاهز تقريباً.
I want the kind Great-Grandma makes.
أريد النوع الذي تصنعه جدتي الكبرى.
With fried eggs in the soup.
مع بيض مقلي في الحساء.
Okay, Mommy will make eggs.
حسناً، ستُحضّر أمي البيض.
Go to Daddy.
اذهب إلى أبي.
Come on.
تعال.
How many do you want?
كم عدد القطع التي تريدها؟
One?
واحد؟
One and a half.
واحد ونصف.
Okay.
تمام.
How many for you?
كم عدد القطع التي تحتاجها؟
Two.
اثنين.
Then I'll have one and a half too.
ثم سأتناول واحدة ونصف أيضاً.
Xingheng.
شينغهنغ.
What does that add up to?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
Five.
خمسة.
You are so smart.
أنت ذكي جداً.
So clever.
ذكي جداً.
Come on.
تعال.
Daddy, your name has
يا أبي، اسمك
five "woods" in it.
خمسة "أشجار" فيها.
You even figured that out?
هل توصلت إلى ذلك أصلاً؟
It does have a lot of "woods".
إنها تحتوي على الكثير من "الغابات".
She's improved so much.
لقد تحسنت كثيراً.
She can
بإمكانها
write all our names
اكتب أسماءنا جميعاً
very beautifully.
جميل جداً.
Really?
حقًا؟
Mommy's name is really hard to write.
اسم أمي صعب الكتابة حقاً.
Really, I can write it.
في الحقيقة، أستطيع كتابتها.
Let me show you.
دعني أريك.
Okay.
تمام.
(Nie Xiguang, Lin Yusen)
(ني شيغوانغ، لين يوسن)
Yusen,
يوسن،
do you remember
هل تذكر
that when we
ذلك عندما
first started dating,
بدأنا المواعدة أولاً،
you sent me a WeChat message,
لقد أرسلت لي رسالة عبر تطبيق وي تشات،
saying your name lacked sunlight
قول اسمك يفتقر إلى ضوء الشمس
with too much "wood"
مع الكثير من "الخشب"
and asked me to bring you light?
وطلبت مني أن أجلب لك النور؟
Did I?
هل فعلت ذلك؟
Yes, you did.
نعم، لقد فعلت.
Don't play dumb.
لا تتظاهر بالغباء.
I also remember every word
أتذكر كل كلمة أيضاً
you've ever said.
لقد قلتَ هذا من قبل.
♪All this time you're in my mind♪
♪ طوال هذا الوقت أنت في بالي ♪
♪I dream of when I'll hold you every day♪
♪أحلم باليوم الذي سأحتضنك فيه كل يوم♪
♪When it won't be a scene that fades away♪
♪عندما لا يكون مشهداً يتلاشى♪
It's for you.
هذا من أجلك.
♪We'll find our way back to when♪
♪سنجد طريقنا للعودة إلى ذلك الزمن♪
♪Through all the times we were getting thru and learnt we're meant to be♪
♪خلال ​​كل الأوقات التي مررنا بها، تعلمنا أننا مقدر لنا أن نكون معًا♪
♪Would we ever be close, you and me♪
هل سنكون قريبين يوماً ما، أنا وأنت؟
♪Oh, wherever you are, whatever you want♪
♪أينما كنت، ومهما أردت♪
♪Don't hesitate to call me, just let me know♪
لا تتردد في الاتصال بي، فقط أخبرني بما تريد
♪I hope you'll never forget♪
♪أتمنى ألا تنسى أبداً♪
(The sunlight I want to give you)
(ضوء الشمس الذي أريد أن أمنحك إياه)
(is a dazzling moment.)
(إنها لحظة مبهرة.)
♪Every moment of every day♪
♪كل لحظة من كل يوم♪
(It's every ordinary and trivial thing.)
(إنه كل شيء عادي وتافه.)
♪Oh can you feel my heart's with you♪
♪هل تشعر بقلبي معك؟♪
♪If you ever wanna know♪
♪إذا أردت أن تعرف يوماً♪
(It's the first ray of sunlight)
(إنها أول شعاع من أشعة الشمس)
(at dawn each morning.)
(عند الفجر كل صباح.)
♪Would we ever be close, you and me♪
هل سنكون قريبين يوماً ما، أنا وأنت؟
(It will also be the last glow)
(سيكون هذا هو التوهج الأخير أيضاً)
(of the sunset many years from now.)
(غروب الشمس بعد سنوات عديدة من الآن.)
♪Don't hesitate to call me, just let me know♪
لا تتردد في الاتصال بي، فقط أخبرني بما تريد
♪I hope you'll never forget♪
♪أتمنى ألا تنسى أبداً♪
♪My heart has only you♪
قلبي لا يملك سواك
♪Every moment of every day♪
♪كل لحظة من كل يوم♪
♪Our love's gonna find a way♪
حبنا سيجد طريقه
♪A gathering storm above♪
♪عاصفة تتجمع في الأعلى♪
♪A winding path to trace♪
♪مسار متعرج يجب تتبعه♪
♪Countless stops along the way♪
♪محطات لا حصر لها على طول الطريق♪
♪Love shouldn't rush today♪
♪لا ينبغي للحب أن يتعجل اليوم♪
♪Has yesterday's rain stopped?♪
هل توقف مطر الأمس؟
♪Today the sun shines bright♪
♪اليوم تشرق الشمس ساطعة♪
♪I who once stood in the corner's light♪
♪أنا الذي وقفتُ ذات يوم في ضوء الزاوية♪
♪Wishing to follow you out of sight♪
♪أتمنى أن أتبعك حتى أختفي عن الأنظار♪
♪How long to wait if we miss once more?♪
♪كم من الوقت سننتظر إذا أخطأنا مرة أخرى؟♪
♪My heart beats only for you♪
قلبي ينبض من أجلك وحدك
♪Through rushing crowds, we made our way♪
♪ شقنا طريقنا وسط الحشود المتدفقة ♪
♪Now holding your hands♪
♪ الآن أمسكوا بأيديكم ♪
♪Holding tight, embracing soft♪
♪تمسك بقوة، واحتضن بلطف♪
♪To guard your gentle smile aloft♪
♪لحماية ابتسامتك الرقيقة عالياً♪
♪Over countless hurdles, we prevailed♪
♪تجاوزنا عقبات لا حصر لها، وانتصرنا♪
♪Now meeting eyes that never failed♪
♪الآن نلتقي بعيون لم تخيب ظننا قط♪
♪No retreat, no fear of winter's cold♪
♪لا تراجع، لا خوف من برد الشتاء♪
♪The sun shines on you♪
♪الشمس تشرق عليك♪
♪And me♪
♪وأنا♪
♪Dreams realized, dreams broken, dreams fade♪
♪أحلام تتحقق، أحلام تتحطم، أحلام تتلاشى♪
♪They're only dreams we've made♪
♪إنها مجرد أحلام صنعناها♪
♪Awake to streets aglow♪
♪استيقظ على شوارع متوهجة♪
♪With me beside you as you go♪
♪معي بجانبك وأنت تمضي♪
♪Skies darken, gloom descends, night falls♪
♪تُظلم السماء، وينزل الظلام، ويحلّ الليل♪
♪It's only rain, after all♪
♪إنها مجرد أمطار، في نهاية المطاف♪
♪We push the window wide to see skies so blue♪
نفتح النافذة على مصراعيها لنرى السماء الزرقاء الصافية
♪There'll always be me and you♪
♪سنبقى أنا وأنت دائمًا♪